Yesterday I forgot. Greetings to all viewers
hôm qua quên Xin kính chào quý vị đang
watching the program. As you know, you are already aware.
xem chương trình bình thường cũng biết
Those of you standing in the car, you can see that
rồi Các bạn đang đứng trên xe cùng tiếp
I am contributing to the Ba Vang Pagoda
xúc thấy mình để tăng chùa Ba Vàng hộp
charity, which is a golden color. I am Loc Hoa, a test of the elephant's completion of the constitution, the name, the heart, the nature, the perfection. I am contributing gold to the charity trip to Central Vietnam, to
chuyến từ thiện Hướng Về Miền Trung cho
support and protect those
và ủng hộ và con được bảo vệ trong đang
suffering from the current natural disaster of floods. At
chịu khó khăn bởi thiên tai lũ lụt gây
over 9 o'clock, our team
ra hiện tại và hơn 9 giờ và Đoàn ta có
arrived in Ha Tinh province and will
mặt tại địa bàn tỉnh Hà Tĩnh và Đoàn sẽ
travel throughout the night to arrive in
chuyển suốt đêm để kịp thời có mặt tại
Quang Nam province early tomorrow morning.
tỉnh Quảng Nam trong sáng sớm ngày mai
Now, there is a small cultural program
bây giờ có một chương trình văn nghệ nhỏ
to boost the morale of all
để có một tinh thần cho toàn thể các
members. This program will be led by the head of the
thành viên chương trình này sẽ do trưởng
team's relations, Hoang Chinh. I am next to you,
ban quan hệ của Đoàn là hoàng chính
but now I am
quyền ở bên cạnh con nhưng bây giờ đã
very grateful and also feel inspired. Please
rất là lời nói dối và cũng cảm ứng dụng
watch and enjoy.
sẽ cùng đón xem và thân Xin chào cô chủ
Greetings to the head of the team. Greetings to all members
nhiệm Xin chào tất cả các thành viên
of the charity team and greetings to the
trong đoàn đi làm từ thiện và Xin chào
audience. Yes,
quý vị khán giả vâng
now we would like to
ở nhà bây giờ thì chúng con xin được gửi
begin the cultural program.
mở đầu cho chương trình văn nghệ chúng
We would like to sing to express our gratitude to our
ta xin gửi về hát để kính tri ân trên sư
master. The song is...  With gratitude to our
phụ bài hát được mang tên Kính tri ân sư
master, we humbly sing
phụ và con xin thì lại trống đồng hát to
this song with the drum to send our sincere respect
bài hát này để gửi tâm thành kính của
to our master. Yes,
chúng ta tới sư phụ ạ ạ
yes, in the past, we loved more when
Ừ thì đến trên xưa đã yêu hơn khi sử
using this, a girl came into being, due to fate, how did fate come about?
dụng này đã ra một cô là do Nhân Duyên
And now, what is there when we should
ạ Và bây giờ mà còn đã có gì khi ta nên
ask to share life, I still remember, still
xin chia đời tôi còn nhớ như thế vẫn dịu
gentle, oh, this memory...
dàng cuối ơi này nỗi nhớ
Yes, what is there here? This has passed, I cried,
Ừ có gì đây Thế này đã qua tôi đã khóc
you loved me as usual, the
anh thương em như thường à
young author just prayed, using the mirror to
tác giả trẻ chỉ là cầu dùng kính trên
keep the sadness, so far away, she is because of you, what a
giữ buồn thay đã xa lắm cô là do em gì
way, crawling far away, the mirror, the cake, now the
cách riêng bò ra xa kính bánh chết giờ
hand, the small suffering is due to the Quan
còn tay đã gian nhỏ khổ là do than Quan
Thanh Duong, peace and now hidden away, when
Thanh Đường An lành và nay dấu đi khi
the diseases on the matter still have to be, how life still has, a hereditary person,
những bệnh trên sự còn phải đã sao đời
the child asks to share laughter,
a di truyền người con xin chia cười cùng
waiting for the court to bring the person to replace the person, the person who replaces the
chờ tòa đưa người thay thận thiết con
gentle Quan, the person who flies really,
ngườithay Quân dịu dàng người bay thật
for the people still on the road, not a
đó cho dân còn trên con đường không câu
green sentence, we humbly thank you, the person who
xanh hỗ chúng con xin tri ân người chua
only hides down, still doing, please let the pregnant woman come
chỉ Ẩn xuống còn làm xin cho thai lại
up again, people need it,
lên người ta cần thiết
everyone sees sadness, gentle skin, this person is
mọi người thấy buồn dịu da người đây vật
more for us  The child on a
hơn nữa cho chúng con trên một đường tâm
green central line supports us, what are you, brother?
cầu xanh hỗ chúng con gì anh người chúng
We ask where to replace you, sister?
con chúng con xin đâu thay thế chị gần
Clap loudly for the next song, for 8
vỗ tay thật lớn bài hát tiếp theo để 8
months, the law, the flower, then right after this,
tháng pháp luật hoa thì ngay sau đây
we will come to the song Chrysanthemum.
chúng ta sẽ cùng đến với bài hát Cúc Hoa
Brother, you don't have any words, and your friend,
anh cũng không lời gì và cô bạn anh đau
where is the pain? No matter how much, it's not thanks to that suffering, it's
đâu có nhiêu cũng không phải nhờ đó là
also a hundred sorrows, crying at the beginning,
khổ cũng vào là bộ trăm Thu Sầu khóc đầu
difficulties, not giving up, the heart, giving up,
khó khăn không nản lòng đàn lòng đầu bỏ
getting healthy, just over, she is An, at
thôi được khỏe vừa qua em nó là con An
the end, if
cuối
anyone needs her, and where is An, oh no,
có ai cần cũng và đâu là bò An ôi không
Uncle, where is it, 123. If it is to encourage four
Bác bật đâu mà 123 Nếu là động viên bốn
people, loving her, simply waiting,
người yêu thương cô đơn giản 6 đợi chờ
don't overdo it, there is no one, where is it, where is
Đừng quá rồi đâu có ai đâu vào đâu có
he happy, still at the beginning of autumn, or where is it,
anh vui còn đầu thu được hoặc ở đâu có
going through and where is not happy, really a lot,
ra qua và đâu là không vui thật nhiều đã
that is happiness. I
đó là vui
mean, I am, together, I, the love
Ý tôi là tôi là tôi cùng nhau tôi Tình
of life, Le, passed on, material things, where is it, flowers,
Đời Lê truyền tài vật đâu có thế hoa
congratulations, the club, the golden fortune,
chúc mừng con câu lạc bộ Phúc vàng có em
where is she, too drunk, even though it helps everyone, the
đâu say quá dù đỡ cho mọi người câu lạc
club is also golden, still giving up eating, really high,
bộ cũng vàng còn bỏ ăn thôi tự thật cao
going through the club, the golden chrysanthemum club,
trải qua câu lạc bộ cúc vàng câu lạc bộ
An, I, the golden lump club, do I give up, brother?
An tôi câu lạc bộ cục vàng có làm bỏ anh
Yes  I'm making a set of Buddhist rituals, a great monk,
Ừ tôi làm bộ Phúc đàn đại đức người bất
unexpectedly saying a sentence at the temple, always together,
ngờ câu tại chùa ban luôn còn nhau thì
we'll do sports, father, always share pain, together we'll sing love songs,
ta thể thao bố thương đau luôn cùng nhau
so that there's love, my dear, Miss
tình ca để câu có thương anh ơi là cô
Cúc, caring, a budding flower, Bobby, going back to the
Cúc quan tâm tu nụ hoa chưa Bobby Về
beloved Central Vietnam, yes,
Miền Trung thân yêu lên à
yes
ừ ừ